http://www.hiway.org/about/privacy-and-security/index.html

Skip to main content
Allowed domains:
https://www.hiwaymortgage.com,https://www.loanliner.com,https://www.hiwayautosale.org,http://www.hiwayautosale.org,https://hiwayautosale.org,http://hiwayautosale.org,https://workforcenow.adp.com,https://hiway.everfi-next.net,https://chat.hiway.org,https://onlinebanking.hiway.org,https://hiwayfcu.na1.echosign.com,https://www.billpaysite.com,https://mcompany.cld.bz,https://www.hockeykids4kids.org,https://app.loanspq.com,https://apptest.loanspq.com,https://litho.silvercloudinc.com,https://info.hiway.org,https://web.baconpay.com,https://app.acuityscheduling.com/
First party domains:
http://www.hiway.org,https://www.hiway.org,http://hiway.org,https://hiway.org,https://hiwaycm1.percussion.marketing,https://dev-hiwaycm1-percussion.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com,http://dev-hiwaycm1-percussion.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com
Confirmation message:
This link leads to a third-party site not governed by Hiway Credit Union. Please see our third-party sites disclosure for more info.\n\nPlease click on OK to continue, or CANCEL to go back.
Online Banking Login
651.291.1515
Save
Health Savings Account
Money Market Savings
Share Savings Account
Certificates
Youth Savings Account
Business Services and Lending Team
ATM and Branch LocationsBanking ToolsContact UsWork at HiwayAbout Hiway
Welcome to the new Hiway Credit Union! Find out more about our charter change and new look.
Hiway Federal Credit Union
Login
Menu
For You
For Your Business
ATM and Branch LocationsBanking ToolsContact UsWork at HiwayAbout Hiway
Save
Health Savings Account
Money Market Savings
Share Savings Account
Certificates
Youth Savings Account
Education Savings Account
Retirement Savings
Login to Online Banking
SaveWatch your money grow and build a foundation for financial success.See all savings optionsSee rates
Savings
Money Market Savings
Youth Savings
Certificates
Education Savings
Health Savings
Retirement Savings
Investment Services
SpendConvenient and safe access to your funds, anywhere, anytime.See all spending optionsSee rates
Free Checking
Hi Yield Checking
Benefits Plus® Checking
Minnesota Wild Free Checking
Debit Cards
Our new Hi Yield Checking lets you earn great dividends while you spend
BorrowPlanning to replace your car, make home improvements, purchase a home or go to school? We have all your lending options right here.See all borrowing optionsMake a paymentSee rates
Mortgage Loans
Home Equity Loans
Home Solar Loans
Auto Loans
Student Loans
Recreational Vehicle Loans
Personal Loans
Credit Cards
If your budget is a little tight for the upcoming holidays, we can help cover your expenses this season
ManageTools to help you make the most of your money, no matter where you are.See all options for managing your money
Account Access
Make a Payment
Direct Deposit
Order Checks
Wire Transfers
Insurance
Safe Deposit Boxes
Forms & Applications
Money Tracker can help you stick to your budget over the holidays with spending targets
LearnResources, events and tools to help you master your finances.See how we can help
Momentum
Financial Education Center
Seminars and Events
Pig-e App
Financial Calculators
Payroll Calendars
Credit Counseling
We are happy to introduce Hiway’s Pig-e App — a new way to help kids pig out on saving money!
Business SavingsLet your excess cash work for your business.See business savings optionsSee rates
Business Savings
Business Money Market Savings
Business Certificates
Business Investments
SpendConvenient, secure spending for your business needs.See all business spending optionsSee rates
Business Checking
Club and Nonprofit Checking
Business Debit Cards
BorrowCustomized financing to help drive growth.See all business borrowing options
Business Credit Card
Commercial Lines of Credit
Commercial Real Estate Loans
Equipment Financing
Commercial Vehicle Financing
ManageFast, powerful, 24/7 access to your accounts.See all options for managing your money
Account Access
Business Services
Cash Management
Merchant Visa® Services
Order Checks
Insurance
LearnThe knowledge to manage all your business' money.See all financial education resources
Momentum
Financial Education
Seminars and Events
Financial Calculators
Payroll Calendars
Credit Counseling
Home
About Hiway
Privacy & Security
Privacy PolicyHiway respects the privacy of our members and we are dedicated to maintaining the confidentiality of your nonpublic personal financial information. Our Privacy Policy applies to both current and former members.Website Privacy StatementHiway is committed to respecting your online privacy and recognizes your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (Personal Information) you share with us. Our Website Privacy Statement applies to anyone that uses our website.Online Banking SecurityLearn about the security measures we employ at Hiway to keep your financial data secure.Protect Your Online IdentityConducting your financial transactions online can actually decrease your chances of becoming a victim of identity theft, but you still need to be cautious. Following a few additional steps can drastically reduce your chances of falling victim to online fraud.Protect Yourself from MalwareMalicious software targeting online banking users is evolving and on the rise. Malware can find its way onto your computer through spam, phishing emails and malicious websites. Learn about malware and how to keep your computer from being infected.Identity Theft PreventionAs with all crimes, you can't guarantee that you'll never be a victim, but you can minimize your risk by managing your personal information wisely. If you receive a notice or hear of a data breach, here are steps you can take from the Federal Trade Commission to protect yourself.Reporting Identity TheftHaving your identity stolen can make you feel like you've lost all control. If your information has been stolen or scammed, you have an opportunity to regain control and prevent the further misuse of that information, if you can take action quickly.
Routing Number: 296075933
651.291.1515
Live Chat
Video Chat
Hiway Federal Credit Union
DisclosuresPrivacy and Security
© 2020 Hiway Credit Union - All Rights Reserved
'
